wlu.edu 2011-05-05

# Privacy Policy :: Washington and Lee University

Home > Privacy Policy

We respect your privacy, and we're willing to stand by our words. If you have any concerns about our collection and use of information obtained while you use our Web site, please read through this short description of our information handling practices. If you still have concerns or wish to contact us in connection to privacy issues not raised in this statement, then please feel free to send us a note. 

#### Concerns/More Information 

Please contact us with any concerns or questions via email at [webcomments@wlu.edu](mailto:webcomments@wlu.edu) or through the mail. 

> Office of Communications   
> Attn: Web Editor   
> 2 Lee Ave.   
> Washington and Lee University   
> Lexington, VA 24450 

#### Constitution & Application 

The W&L Web site (defined by the domain name www.wlu.edu) is comprised of any publicly accessible (as defined by an industry standard HTTP or HTTPS connection) files and/or computer code. 

This privacy policy applies only to the W&L Web site, and not to any additional Web sites that may be linked to from the W&L Web site. The Communications Office is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of those sites. 

#### Automatic Information Collection 

Our servers automatically collect information about your Web browser, proxy or firewall servers, and other relevant information about your browsing session on our site. Please be aware that none of this information can be used by anyone to identify you. We use this session information--including your specific Web browser vendor and version, the type of computer operating system you are using, and the IP address of your computer--to help us better design and structure our Web site. In the event of a security breach to our servers, we may provide this information to the relevant state and federal authorities. 

#### Personal Information 

We only collect personally identifiable information, such as your name and email address, when you volunteer it to us, say through submitting an email list subscription form. We retain the right to store and analyze this information indefinitely in order to examine and improve our Web services. We do not provide any third parties with any voluntarily or otherwise personally identifiable information, meaning we do not sell, rent, or market personal data about you to third parties. 

If we ever decide to change our policy on using personally identifiable information, we will inform each individual who we have recorded as submitting such information to us. An email message, containing the text of the policy change, sent to each recorded address will constitute such notice. We will provide each recipient with a method of unsubscribing, or opting-out, of the policy change. 

#### Cookies 

In an effort to better service you through our Web site, we may store small amounts of information on your computer through the use of cookies. Our Web site does not require that you grant us the right to store cookies on your computer. If you do not wish to grant us this right, consult the documentation provided with your Web browser to turn off the appropriate "accept cookies" feature in your browser. The settings on cookies contained in your browser constitute a grant of permission (or lack thereof) for us to store information on your computer. 

We follow all industry standards in constructing and storing cookies with your browser. Thus it is your browser vendor's responsibility to provide for secure and appropriate cookie storage mechanisms. 

#### Appropriate Communications 

We reserve the right to contact you without prior notice through the use of email. These unsolicited communications will address matters to do only with the storage of personal information on our servers and/or other business matters. These communications are strictly business-oriented in nature and will never address marketing or promotional matters. We do not support, approve of, or otherwise engage in the sending of unsolicited bulk marketing and promotional email messages, or spam email. 

#### Solicited Email-based Marketing/Communications 

We may, at times, send you marketing or promotional email messages to inform you of new services and/or product announcements. These communications are considered supplemental to any emails we may send you regarding subscriptions or concerns about your use of the W&L Web site. We send these messages to you only if you have expressly agreed to allow us to send these messages to you. In each email message we send, we will always provide you with the ability to unsubscribe, or otherwise opt-out, of these communications. Please follow the instructions contained in those messages for opting-out of this marketing service. 

We do not support, approve of, or otherwise engage in the sending of unsolicited bulk marketing and promotional email messages, or spam email. 

#### Notification of Changes 

We reserve the right to change our privacy policy at any time. We will always immediately republish this statement to reflect those changes. An up-to-date privacy statement can always be found at this location. Unless otherwise noted in this statement, posting appropriately changed versions of this statement at this location will constitute sufficient notice of those changes in our privacy policy.
